Muhammad Azmi

Jakarta Pusat, DKI Jakarta | 081315927439 | azmi.filkom@gmail.com <u>linkedin</u> - <u>medium</u> - <u>github</u> - <u>portfolio</u> @azmi6298

About Me

My name is Muhammad Azmi, graduated from Universitas Brawijaya as Bachelor of Computer Science (S.Kom) in 2019. Right now, I work as a full stack web developer at PT. Ukirama Solusi Indonesia. I have experience as a front end web developer at RuangUMKM, Gank Global, coding mentor at infiniteclass.id, freelancer lead developer at cataloq.co, and mobile app developer at PT. Aristi Jasadata. I am very passionate about web development and currently exploring front-end world extensively. I have a lot of experience in the field of software development for the past 2 years and have a good understanding of web application development, relational databases, and basic live production server deployment. I also love to share my progress and experiences when learning new things through my Medium channel.

Skills

- Ruby on Rails
- Javascript (Node.js)
- PostgreSQL

- Vue.js / Nuxt.js
- React / Next.js
- TailwindCSS

Work Experience

RuangUMKM (Indonesia, Remote)

Front End Developer - Freelance (October 2021-December 2021)

- Implementing front end for marketplace project using Nuxt.js
- Deploying the production app into Google Cloud Platform (GCP) App Engine

Gank Global (Indonesia, Remote)

Front End Developer - Freelance (July 2021-August 2021)

- Implementing front end for various feature based on Figma screen using Nuxt.js
- Styling pages using TailwindCSS

@infiniteclass.id - Programming Fundamentals with Javascript (Indonesia)

Coding Mentor (February 2021-May 2021)

- Collaborating with other mentors and facilitator to build learning modules
- Observing progress of mentees during live class session
- Creating assignment to mentees and giving feedback
- Empowering mentees to learn and develop their basic coding skills

cataloq.co (Indonesia)

Lead Developer - Freelance (August 2020-March 2021)

- Designing and implementing various feature into a marketplace application using Express.js and PostgreSQL
- Fully responsible for integrating and managing repository for backend and frontend app
- Coordinating with product owner and frontend developers
- Prepare and deploy live server, set up custom domain and integrating mailer service
- Maintaining live server, production-ready app to be stable and run smoothly

PT. Ukirama Solusi Indonesia (Jakarta, Indonesia)

Full Stack Web Developer (September 2019-now)

- Designing and implementing various function into ERP application using Ruby on Rails, Angular, and PostgreSQL
- Doing QA, peer reviewing code, debugging, and fixing various types of bugs
- Coordinating with business analyst, UI UX designer, and business consultant
- Deploying live server for various clients
- Achievement: Being contributor on major release of UkiramaERP version 1.x and 2.x, building a brand new order management system from scratch for one of the biggest F&B company in Indonesia

PT. Aristi Jasadata

Android Developer (Internship) (July 2018-August 2018)

- Implementing function into mobile banking application using Java (Android Studio)
- Designing intuitive user interface and user experience
- Building production-ready app for various clients to deployed to Google Play Store
- Achievement: Implementing one of core feature on the app, Deposit Account feature

Education

Universitas Brawijaya (2015-2019)

S1 Teknik Informatika - GPA 3.66

SMAN 77 Jakarta (2012-2015)

Natural Science